The Guide to the Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hiteman Leather Company records, 1898-1968
2969
Hiteman Leather Company.
30 cubic ft.
Correspondence, records, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, financial and business records for the Hiteman Leather Company, West Winfield, New York, including information on shoe industry trends, industry newsletters and detailed material concerning daily maintenance of a tannery operation. Also includes correspondence and reports on sanitary sewage treatment and water pollution, 1960-1967.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, financial and business records for the Hiteman Leather Company, West Winfield, New York, including information on shoe industry trends, industry newsletters and detailed material concerning daily maintenance of a tannery operation. Financial records include invoices, cash receipts, checks and cash payments, daybooks, quarterly financial statements, receipted bills and remittances. Production records include skin lot orders, skins received and processed, processing, color and grade of leather, soak books, dying processes and color formulas. Also includes correspondence and reports on sanitary sewage treatment and water pollution, 1960-1967. Chief correspondents for the company, 1915-1967, are William H. Hiteman, George Hiteman, Ralph Toye, Ralph Pleatman, Gordon Davis and Allen N. Bennett.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hiteman Leather Company.; Hiteman, William.; Hiteman, George.; Toye, Ralph.; Pleatman, Ralph.; Davis, Gordon.; Bennett, Allen N.
Subjects:
Boots and shoes--Trade and manufacture.; Boots and shoes--Materials.; Hides and skins.; Leather.; Sewage--Environmental aspects.; Shoes.; Tanning.; Water--Pollution.; Water quality management.
- J.C. Andresen & Co., Inc.: Correspondence, reports, bills., 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "A": Correspondence, news bulletin, pamphlets, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Boot & Shoe Recorder: Correspondence, bulletins, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- F. Brown Shoe Company: Correspondence, orders, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bureau of Animal Industry: Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Calf Tanners' Association: Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- "B": Correspondence, bulletins, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "C": Correspondence, orders, bill of lading, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Densten Felt & Hair Co.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "D": Correspondence, reports, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "E": Correspondence, reports, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Feakes Mercantile Agency, Inc.: Reports, correspondence, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- First Citizens' Bank & Trust Co. - Trends: News letters, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- First Citizens Bank & Trust Co.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "F": Correspondence, leather samples, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ganey, Hornung & Hall: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Getz Bros. & Co.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Daniel Green Company: Correspondence, invoices, leather samples, orders, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- "G": Correspondence, leather samples, news bulletin, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- "H": Correspondence, sample, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- William B. Heald & Co. May 1939: Correspondence, leather sample (Box 1, Folder 21)
- William B. Heald & Co., April 1939: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 22)
- William B. Heald & Co., March 1939: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 23)
- William B. Heald & Co., February 1939: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 24)
- William B. Heald & Co., January 1939: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 25)
- William B. Heald & Co., December 1938: Inventory, correspondence (Box 1, Folder 26)
- William B. Heald & Co. November 1938: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 27)
- William B. Heald & Co., October 1938: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 28)
- William B. Heald & Co., September 1938: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 29)
- William B. Heald & Co., Acct. sales: Accounts, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- William B. Heald & Co., Orders: Orders, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Heinsheimer Bros., Inc.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Herman Hollander, Inc.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Hiteman Leather Co.: Correspondence, notes, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Hudson-Mohawk Mutual Casualty Co., Reports: Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hudson-Mohawk Mutual Casualty Co.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- "I": Correspondence, bulletins, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Johnstown Wool Shoe Co.: Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- "J": Reprint, correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- "K": Correspondence, form letters, orders, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Department of Labor: Correspondence, reporta, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- "L": Correspondence, form letters, leather samples, orders, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- "R": Correspondence, sales literature, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Smaller War Plants Corporation: Correspondence, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Social Security: Correspondence, employment applications, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Armand Schnoll, Inc.: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- The Shelby Salesbuck Co.: Correspondence, sales material, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Swan Shoe Company: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "S": Correspondence, sales material order invoices, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Tanners' Council of American, August 1947: News letters (Box 2, Folder 7a)
- Tanners' Council of America, July 1947: News letter, weekly reports (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Tanners' Council of America, June 1947: Newsletters, reports (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Tanners' Council of America, May 1947: Reports, newsletter, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Tanners' Council of America, April 1947: Newsletters, reports (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Tanners' Council of America, March 1947: Council news, reports, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Tanners' Council of America, February 1947: Newsletter, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Textile Color Card Assoc.: Newsletter, program booklet, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Treasury Department: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "T": Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- United Eastern Coal Sales Corp.: Correspondence, bills, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- "U": Correspondence, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- "V": Correspondence, contracts, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- War Production Board: Correspondence, WPB handouts, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- War Production Board Preference Rating Certificate: Application, correspondence, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- A.L. Webster & Co., August 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 22)
- A.L. Webster & Co., July 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 23)
- A.L. Webster & Co., June 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 24)
- A.L. Webster & Co., May 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 25)
- A.L. Webster & Co., April 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 26)
- A.L. Webster & Co., March 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 27)
- A.L. Webster & Co., February 1947: Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 28)
- "W": Correspondence, enclosure, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- J.C. Anderson & Co.: Correspondence, newsletters, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- American Appraisal Co.: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Bureau of Animal Industry: Correspondence, reports, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- "A": Correspondence, sale, literature, enclosure, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- "B": Correspondence, enclosures, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Department of Commerce: Report, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Calf Tanners' Assoc.: Correspondence, reports, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- "C": Correspondence, enclosures, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- J.J. Doorley & Co.: Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- The Martin Dennis Co.: Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- E.I. du Pont de Numours & Co. Grasselli Chemicals Dept.: Orders, packing sheet, 1 correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- "D": Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Endicott Johnson Corp., orders: Purchase orders, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Endicott Johnson Corp.: Correspondence, statements, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- "E": Correspondence enclosures, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Feakes Mercantile Agency: Correspondence and reports, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- First Citizens Bank and Trust Co.: Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- First Citizens Bank and Trust Co., Trends: Newsletter, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- "F": Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Daniel Green Co.: Correspondence, 1936-1397 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Ganey Hornung Co.: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- General Dyestuff Corp.: Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- "G": Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Mr. George J. Hiteman (Hitemand Leather Co., Inc.): Correspondence, telegrams and copies, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Hartford Steam Engine & Boiler: Inspection reports, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, February 1937 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, orders, January 1937 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Wm. B. Heald Co.: Correspondence, orders, December 1936 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, orders, November 1936 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, orders, October 1936 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, orders, September 1936 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co.: Correspondence, August 1936 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Hudson-Mohawk Mutual Casualty Reports: Workman's Compensation, claim decisions, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Hudson-Mohawk Mutual Casualty Correspondence: Correspondence, compensation check stubs, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Philip Hurvitz: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Hermann Hollander: Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Wm. B. Heald & Co., Account of Sales: Figures, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- "H": Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- "I": Correspondence, enclosures, 1937-1936 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Johnstown Wool Shoe Co.: Correspondence, orders, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- "J": Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- A.S. Krieder Shoe Co.: Correspondence, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- "K": Correspondence, orders, newsletters, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Department of Labor: Correspondence, reports, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- New York State Dept. of Labor, Wage and Hour Report: Reports, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- "L": Correspondence, advertisement layouts, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- were discarded (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
- Textile Color Card Association, Woolen Color Card: 6 covers - wool samples, 1941-1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Textile Color Card Association of the U.S. Color Card: 4 covers, material swatches, 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Textile Color Card Assoc. Colors For Women's gloves: 1 card, material swatches, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Tanners' Council of America Fashion Guide-official leather colors: 1 booklet, notes on leather colors, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Textile Color Card Assoc.: 2 booklets, material samples, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Report-Met. New York Area: Reports, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Report-Pa.-Md. Area: Reports, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Report-New England Area: Reports, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Report-Upstate New York Area: Reports, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Report-Ohio Area: Report, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Report-Chicago-Nashville Area: Unused report forms, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Report-California Area: Unused forms, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Verdekal Accounts, March 1958: Fiscal statement (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Sales Analysis: Salemen, territories, figures, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Spring-1959: Tanners' Council of America Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Spring-1958, Leather show: Printed matter for show, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Fall-1957, Leather show: Preliminary information, show directory, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Spring-1957: Reports for leather show, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Fall-1956: Reports, correspondence (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Spring-1956: Reports, correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Fall-1955: Reports, notes, 1954-1955 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Spring-1955: Reports, notes, hotel reservations, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Fall-1954: Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Spring-1954: Reports, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Government Contract Specs: Printed specifications, 1950-1958 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Maple Syrup Mailing list: Correspondence, list, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Waxey Calf: Notes, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Leather show: Booklets, reports, notes, 1947-1959 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Advertisements, Trade Magazines: Ads, advertising rates, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Color Committee: Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Contract tanning "General Shoe": Correspondence, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Corrugated Boxes: Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Credit Rating Concerns: Dun & Bradstreet enclosures, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Bark Quotation: Correspondence, preliminary figures, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Feakes Reports on California Accounts: Reports, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Old Price Lists, 1952-1953, 1954: Price lists, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- "The Story of Leather": Correspondence, film reservation, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- "H": Chemical reports, correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- "I": Correspondence, enclosures, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "J": Correspondence, orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- "Kaufmann Trading Corporation": Auction results, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- "K": Correspondence, orders, newsletters, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- "Alpine Leather Co.": Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Department of Labor-NYS: Department information, forms, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Department of Labor-"Nature of Experience Rating Charges Charts": Charts, claim forms, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Labor Dept. of Wage and Hour Reports-Employment, Labor and home reports, January 1954 to: Reports, notes, 1947-1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- "L": Invoices, orders, correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. Reports": Claim reports, form letters, correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co.": Correspondence, report, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- "Milligan and Higgins Corp.": Correspondence, report of loads, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- "Mutual Shoe Co.": Correspondence, orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- "Hemann Loewensteir, Inc.: Correspondence, orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- "M": Correspondence, invoices, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- "Mc": Correspondence, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- "N": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, newsletter, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- "O": Orders, correspondence, invoices, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- "A.J. &J.O. Pilou, Inc.": Correspondence, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- "Post Office-Registered, Buy Rent, Insurance": Receipts, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- "P": Correspondence, invoices, orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- "R": Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- "P. C. Stevens - Orders": Orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- "P. C. Stevens - November 1957": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- "P. C. Stevens - October 1957": Correspondence, memos, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- "P. C. Stevens - September 1957": Correspondence, memos (Box 4, Folder 27)
- "S": Correspondence, enclosures, leather sample, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- "Tanners Council News": Newsletters, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- "H. T. Tankersley & Co. - Orders": Orders, 1 telegram, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- "H. T. Tankersley & Co. - November 1957": Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- "H. T. Tankersley & Co. - October 1957": Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 32)
- "H. T. Tankersley & Co. - September 1957": Correspondence, report (Box 4, Folder 33)
- "Tanners' Council of America - November 1957": Correspondence, industry report, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- "Tanners' Council of America - Trade Survey Bureau": Weekly reports, correspondence, 1957 - 1958 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- "Tanners' Council of America - September 1957": Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 36)
- "Tanners' Council of America - October 1957": Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 37)
- "Town & Country Shoes": Correspondence, orders, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- "Time Studies": Time studies for several operations, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- "T": Correspondence, orders, leather samples, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- "U": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- "Albert Verdekal - November 1957": Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- "Albert Verdekal - October 1957": Correspondence, invoice (Box 4, Folder 43)
- "V": Correspondence, enclosures, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- "A. L. Webster & Co.": Market reports, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Edmond Weil, Inc.": Correspondence, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- "W": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, invoices, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- "Remittance Statements": Paid invoices, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- "Employment Insurance Information - 1958": Correspondence, insurance forms, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- "Letters to All Agents": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- "Wires": Telegrams, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- "American Appraisal Company": Correspondence, lists and value of machinery, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Co. - 1959": Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 54)
- "Alpine Leather Co. Orders. 1959": Orders, leather samples, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- "Alpine Leather Company": Correspondence, leather samples, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- "A": Correspondence, newsletter, bylaws, Adirondack Tanners Club, orders, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- "Mr. Sidney Brown": Correspondence, reports, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- "B": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- "Hugh Carville - Correspondence": Correspondence, notes, reports, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Correspondence, orders, invoices, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- "C": Correspondence, invoices, orders, enclosures, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- "A. L. Webster & Company 1959": Weekly report on hide market (Box 5, Folder 1)
- "Water Pollution Waste Disposal": Correspondence, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- "W": Orders, correspondence, enclosures, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- "X-Y-Z": Correspondence and enclosures, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- "Remittance Statements 1958": Receipted bills (Box 5, Folder 5)
- "American Appraisal Company": Correspondence, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- "Wires - 1958": Telegrams (Box 5, Folder 7)
- "Letters to All Agents 1958": Correspondence re company reorganization (Box 5, Folder 8)
- "Alpine Leather Company - Orders 1958": Orders, leather sample, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- "Alpine Leather Company 1958": Correspondence, leather samples (Box 5, Folder 10)
- "Aulson Tanning Machinery Company 1958": Correspondence, enclosures, machine instructions (Box 5, Folder 11)
- "A": Correspondence, reports, bills and shipping memos, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- "Boot and Shoe Recorder - 1958": Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 13)
- "B": Correspondence, bills, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- "Correspondence - H. F. Carville": Correspondence, sales reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- "Carlisle Shoe Company": Orders, bills, correspondence, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- "C": Correspondence, orders, bills, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- "Wm. P. Davidson - Orders 1958": Orders (Box 5, Folder 18)
- "William P. Davidson - 1958": Correspondence, sales reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- "Dalson, Inc. 1958": Correspondence, orders, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- "Howard Dietrich & Son, Inc.": Market reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- "Thomas Dorrity - 1958": Sales reports, correspondence, orders, leather samples, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- "Disciplinary Action": Correspondence, report, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- "Department of Labor. N.Y.S.": Reports, forms, notice of hearings, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- "D": Correspondence, orders, enclosures, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- "H. Elkan & Co.": Hide market report, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Reports - 1958": Correspondence, insurance claim forms, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- "Employers Mutual Liability Insurance Co. of Wisconsin Hudson-Mohawk Branch 1958": Correspondence, reports and general info. (Box 5, Folder 28)
- "Endicott Johnson Corporation": Correspondence, orders, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- "E": Correspondence, invoice orders, enclosures, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- "Feakes Mercantile Agency 1958": Reports (Box 5, Folder 31)
- "First Bank & Trust Company 1958": Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 32)
- "F": Orders, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- "Ganey, Hagar & Company 1958": Correspondence, notes on taxes (Box 5, Folder 34)
- "General Information": Weekly figures on processing of raw material, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- "G": Correspondence, orders, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- "Tom Hartnett - Orders": Orders, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- "Tom Hartnett": Correspondence, sales reports, inventory, notes, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- "Heald & Company 1958": Orders, correspondence (Box 5, Folder 39)
- "Vogel Helmholz": Correspondence, sales information, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- "Hide Sheets - 1958": Records of skins (Box 5, Folder 41)
- "Hospital Plan, Inc. 1958": Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 42)
- "George E. Hymrod, Jr. 1958": Correspondence, sales reports, shipping records (Box 5, Folder 43)
- "H": Contract, reports, orders, correspondence and enclosures, inspection reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- "In Process Inventory": Handwritten inventory figures, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- "I": Correspondence, shipping report, enclosures, maintenance agreements, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- "J": Correspondence, invoices, orders, Leather Bulletin, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- "Kaufman Trading Corp. 1958": Calfskin auction results reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- "K": Correspondence re organization, orders, other correspondence, newsletters, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- "L": Correspondence, invoices, orders, enclosures, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. Reports 1958": Claim forms, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- "Milligan & Higgins Corp. 1958": Shipping records, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- "Metropolitan Life Insurance Co. 1958": Correspondence and enclosure (Box 5, Folder 53)
- "Mutual Shoe Company": Bills, orders, correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- "M": Moving invoices, orders, correspondence and enclosures, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- "Mc": Correspondence and enclosures, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- "Department of Labor 'Nature of Experience Rating Charges' - Charts - 1958": Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- "N": Fire inspection report, correspondence, newsletter, orders, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- "O": Orders, correspondence, enclosures, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- "A.J. & J.O. Pilar, Inc. 1958": Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 60)
- "Post Office Box Rent, Insurance, Registered 1958": Receipts (Box 5, Folder 61)
- "P": Correspondence, enclosures, orders, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- "Q": Correspondence, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- "William P. Davidson Orders - 1959": Orders, correspondence (Box 6, Folder 1)
- "William P. Davidson: Correspondence, reports, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- "Dalsan 1959": Correspondence, claim forms, reports (Box 6, Folder 3)
- "Howard Dietrich & Son: Market reports, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 4)